gospelscoop.com 2009-11-23

# Privacy Policy | GospelScoop Christian Social Bookmarking

Our Privacy Policy  
What This Privacy Policy Covers 

This privacy policy relates to use of the myIchthus Ministry Group web sites including  
<http://www.gospelscoop.com/>

This privacy policy covers how myIchthus Ministry Group (hereafter named 'we') will treat personal information that we collect. Personal information is your information and includes identifiers like your name, address, email address, phone number. 

We will not send you any junk emails. Furthermore we will not send you any information unless you have specifically requested we do so. An exception to this rule will be the initial email validation when you create a new account. 

Children under 13 are not permitted to use the myIchthus Ministry Group websites, and so  
this privacy policy makes no provision for children's use of the site. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Changes to this Privacy Policy 

myIchthus Ministry Group may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information we will send a notice to the primary email address specified in your myIchthus Social Network account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us at:
